{
    "id": "d3b350fe6cfe44efb9a9e314ed8965a9",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Anyone ………………………. do this. (Ability)",
            "description": "We use can to express ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. have married her if I had wanted to. (Unrealized past ability)",
            "description": "Could have + past participle can be used to talk about past events that did not happen.",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "can",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………. go swimming on the weekend. (Possibility)",
            "description": "May is used to indicate possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "will",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was so angry I ………………………… have slapped him.",
            "description": "Could have + past participle can be used to talk about past events that did not happen.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One day, it ………………………. be possible to live on other planets. (Future prediction)",
            "description": "We use will to simply predict future.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Tropical areas ………………………… be very warm throughout the year. (Possibility)",
            "description": "We use can to talk about theoretical possibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Epidemics ……………………….. break out any day. (Theoretical possibility)",
            "description": "We use can to talk about theoretical possibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘There is the doorbell.’ ‘Who ……………………………. it be?’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is Janet?’ ‘She ………………………… be in the basement.’",
            "description": "Can is not used to talk about logical possibility in affirmative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What ………………………….. we do now?’",
            "description": "Shall is used to ask for suggestions. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. see something over there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. help but laugh.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "couldn't",
                "shouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}